Guide to the Stuart Stein papers, [ca. 1960-1995]
Stein, Stuart papers, [ca. 1960-1995]
- Professional Work
  - Other
    - Environmental Impact Statement: Cultural District Plan, City of Rochester, County of Monroe, March 31, 1980 (Box 10, Folder 14)
    - Ross, Hardies, O'Keefe, Babcock & Parsons: P.R. Air Rights (Box 10, Folder 15)
    - Department of Transportation and Public Works, Commonwealth of Puerto Rico: Air Rights (Box 10, Folder 16)
    - A Housing Study and Action Program for Ponce, Puerto Rico, April 1969 (Box 10, Folder 17)
    - Urban Renewal and Housing Administration, Commonwealth of Puerto Rico, May-December 1968 (Box 10, Folder 18)
    - Urban Renewal and Housing Administration, Commonwealth of Puerto Rico, July-December 1969 (Box 10, Folder 19)
    - Stein and Marcou Associates & Office of Urban Renewal, District of Columbia: Democratic Action to Save a Neighborhood (Box 10, Folder 20)
    - Ulrich Franzen and Associates, Architects: Reports (Box 10, Folder 21)
- New York Office of Parks, Recreation & Historic Preservation
  - Misc.
    - Fostering Environmental Stewardship (Box 10, Folder 22)
  - Board for Historic Preservation
    - BHP: Adirondacks (Box 10, Folder 23)
    - BHP: Agenda, Notices, Minutes I., pre-1980 (Box 10, Folder 24)
    - BHP: Agenda, Notices, Minutes II., pre-1980 (Box 10, Folder 25)
    - BHP: Agenda, Notices, Minutes, 1980-1981 (Box 10, Folder 26)
    - BHP: Agenda, Notices, Minutes, 1982-1983 (Box 10, Folder 27)
    - BHP: Agenda, Notices, Minutes, 1984-1985 (Box 10, Folder 28)
    - BHP: Agenda, Notices, Minutes, 1986-1987 (Box 10, Folder 29)
    - BHP: Albany I. (Box 10, Folder 30)
    - BHP: Albany II. (Box 10, Folder 31)
    - BHP: Appointment Letters (Box 10, Folder 32)
    - BHP: Archaeology (Box 11, Folder 1)
    - BHP: Awards (Box 11, Folder 2)
    - BHP: Background Materials (Box 11, Folder 3)
    - BHP: Budget (Box 11, Folder 4)
    - BHP: Budget Presentation, 1986-1987 (Box 11, Folder 5)
    - BHP: Clippings (Box 11, Folder 6)
    - BHP: Committees (Box 11, Folder 7)
    - BHP: Historic Site Committee (Box 11, Folder 8)
    - BHP: Committee on Legislation, 1980-1981 (Box 11, Folder 9)
    - BHP: Committee on Legislation, 1982-1986 (Box 11, Folder 10)
    - BHP: Committee on the Registers, 1976, 1981-1982 (Box 11, Folder 11)
    - BHP: Committee on the Registers, 1983 (Box 11, Folder 12)
    - BHP: Committee on the Registers, 1984-1985 (Box 11, Folder 13)
    - BHP: Cornell University Ag. Quad (Box 11, Folder 14)
    - BHP: Correspondence I., 1980-1981 (Box 11, Folder 15)
    - BHP: Correspondence II., 1980-1981 (Box 11, Folder 16)
    - BHP: Correspondence, 1980-1981 (Box 11, Folder 17)
    - BHP: Correspondence, 1982 (Box 11, Folder 18)
    - BHP: Correspondence, 1983 (Box 11, Folder 19)
    - BHP: Correspondence, 1984-1987, n.d. (Box 11, Folder 20)
    - BHP: FDR Hyde Park Property (Box 11, Folder 21)
    - BHP: Marbletown, 1982 (Box 11, Folder 22)
    - BHP: Membership, Staff Lists, Resumes (Box 11, Folder 23)
    - BHP: Membership (Resignations) (Box 11, Folder 24)
    - BHP: Middletown Budget (Box 11, Folder 25)
    - BHP: Miscellaneous (Box 11, Folder 26)
    - BHP: National Conference of State Historic Preservation Officers (Box 11, Folder 27)
    - BHP: Nomination & Appointment as Member and as Chairman, Letters of Congrat. - Stuart W. Stein (Box 11, Folder 28)
    - BHP: New York State Building Code (Box 11, Folder 29)
    - BHP: Religious Properties Bill, 1982 (Box 11, Folder 30)
    - BHP: Resumes (Box 11, Folder 31)
    - BHP: Stein - For Your Signature (Box 11, Folder 32)
    - BHP: Travel Tax Exemption Certificates (Box 11, Folder 33)
  - Division for Historic Preservation
    - DHP (Box 11, Folder 34)
    - DHP: Landmark Society of Broome County (Box 11, Folder 35)
    - DHP: DHP News (Box 11, Folder 36)
  - State Parks Council
    - State Parks Council (Box 11, Folder 37)
- Community Activities & Service
  - Miscellaneous
    - Broome County, N.Y.: Binghamton - Court House Sq. Hist. District (Box 11, Folder 38)
    - Chemung County, N.Y.: Preservation Study (Box 11, Folder 39)
    - Chenengo County, N.Y. (Box 11, Folder 40)
    - Chenengo County, N.Y.: C.C. Planning & Development Board - Teaching Handbook on Historic Preservation (Draft) (Box 11, Folder 41)
    - Chenengo County, N.Y.: McDonaugh NRI, 1986 (Box 11, Folder 42)
    - Cortland County, N.Y.: Presentation to Homer Congregational Church (Box 11, Folder 43)
    - Luzerne County (Box 16, Folder 16)
    - Monroe County, N.Y.: South East Area Coalition - Rochester, 1973-1974 (Box 11, Folder 44)
  - Tompkins County
    - Tompkins County, N.Y. (Box 11, Folder 45)
    - Tompkins County, N.Y.: Board of Representatives, 1993 (Box 11, Folder 46)
    - Tompkins County, N.Y.: Environmental Management Council, By-Laws (Box 11, Folder 47)
    - Tompkins County, N.Y.: Transportation Commission Planning Committee I., 1977-1978 (Box 11, Folder 48)
    - Tompkins County, N.Y.: Transportation Commission Planning Committee II., 1977-1978 (Box 11, Folder 49)
    - Tompkins County, N.Y.: Transportation Commission Planning Committee, 1979 (Box 11, Folder 50)
    - Tompkins County, N.Y.: "Historic Ithaca", 1981, 1983-1984, n.d. (Box 11, Folder 51)
    - Tompkins County, N.Y.: TOMTRAN - Tompkins County Transportation Services Project - Final Report to Appalachian Regional Commission, January 1985 (Box 11, Folder 52)
    - Tompkins County, N.Y.: Intergovernment Coop. Committee I., 1975-1976 (Box 11, Folder 53)
    - Tompkins County, N.Y.: Intergovernment Coop. Committee II., 1975-1976 (Box 11, Folder 54)
    - Tompkins County, N.Y.: Department of Planning (Box 11, Folder 55)
    - Tompkins County, N.Y.: Department of Planning - Technical Advisory Group, Randy Shew (Box 11, Folder 56)
    - Tompkins County, N.Y.: Ithaca Community Renewal Program - Ithaca Planning Board (Box 12, Folder 1)
    - Tompkins County, N.Y.: Ithaca City School District - Future of Downtown Schools, October 28, 1970 (Box 12, Folder 2)
    - Tompkins County, N.Y.: Ithaca Area Transportation Study (Box 12, Folder 3)
    - Tompkins County, N.Y.: Northeast Area Transit Study Committee, March 26, 1979 (Box 12, Folder 4)
    - Tompkins County, N.Y.: Ithaca Petition - Parking & Transportation, 1975-1976 (Box 12, Folder 5)
    - Tompkins County, N.Y.: Ithaca - Southside Improvement Organization (Box 12, Folder 6)
    - Tompkins County, N.Y.: Ithaca - Statistics (Box 12, Folder 7)
    - Tompkins County, N.Y.: Groton (Box 12, Folder 8)
    - Tompkins County, N.Y.: Lansing (Box 12, Folder 9)
- Professional Activities
  - Advisory Council on Historic Preservation (Box 12, Folder 10)
  - Advisory Council on Historic Preservation (Box 12, Folder 11)
  - Advisory Council on Historic Preservation, 1980 (Box 12, Folder 12)
  - Advisory Council on Historic Preservation: A Report to the President of Congress of the United States, 1973-1974 (Box 12, Folder 13)
  - American Institute of Architects (Box 12, Folder 14)
  - American Institute of Architects: Philadelphia Chapter - Background Readings Related to Architecture and the Built Environment (Box 12, Folder 15)
  - American Institute of Certified Planners (Box 12, Folder 16)
  - American Institute of Planners (Box 12, Folder 17)
  - American Institute of Planners: Teaching Design to Planners - Stuart W. Stein, October 1974 (Box 12, Folder 18)
  - AIP: Journal of the American Institute of Planners, vol. XXVII, no. 1, February 1961 (Box 12, Folder 19)
  - AIP: Planner Notebook, October 1973, June, August & December 1974 (Box 12, Folder 20)
  - AIP: Practicing Planner, December 1976 (Box 12, Folder 21)
  - American Planning Association (Box 12, Folder 22)
  - American Society of Planning Officials (Box 12, Folder 23)
  - American Society of Planning Officials: Ford Fellowship, 1971 (Box 12, Folder 24)
  - American Society of Planning Officials: Ford Fellowships - Proposal, 1972 (Box 12, Folder 25)
  - American Society of Planning Officials: Ford-Minority Fellowship Application, Fall 1973 (Box 12, Folder 26)
  - American Society of Planning Officials: Ford Fellowship I., 1971-1976 (Box 12, Folder 27)
  - American Society of Planning Officials: Ford Fellowship II., 1971-1976 (Box 12, Folder 28)
  - American Society of Planning Officials: Newsletter, August & December 1971 (Box 12, Folder 29)
  - Assist Inc. - Architectural Aid Program: "Housing Within Different Contexts" (Box 12, Folder 30)
  - Association of Collegiate Schools of Planning, 1971-1974 (Box 12, Folder 31)
  - Gallery Association of New York State I. (Box 12, Folder 32)
  - Gallery Association of New York State II. (Box 12, Folder 33)
  - Gap International, Inc. - Tom Kehoe (Box 12, Folder 34)
  - Department of Housing and Urban Development (HUD) (Box 12, Folder 35)
  - HUD: Condominium Study, 1975 (Box 12, Folder 36)
  - HUD: Demonstration Cities Program, 1966 (Box 12, Folder 37)
  - HUD: Housing and Community Development Act, 1974 (Box 12, Folder 38)
  - HUD: Federal Housing Programs - Information (Box 12, Folder 39)
  - HUD: Publications (Box 12, Folder 40)
  - HUD: Publications (Box 12, Folder 41)
  - International Association for the Exchange of Students for Technical Experience (Box 12, Folder 42)
  - International Council of Shopping Centers: 20th Anniversary Advertising Supplement (Box 12, Folder 43)
  - Jay Coalition (Box 12, Folder 44)
  - John Jay Homestead State Historic Site (Box 12, Folder 45)
  - National League of Cities: National Municipal Policy (Box 12, Folder 46)
  - National Endowment for the Arts (NEA), 1977, 1980-1981 (Box 12, Folder 47)
  - National Endowment for the Arts (NEA), 1982 (Box 12, Folder 48)
  - NEA: Architects-in-Schools (Box 12, Folder 49)
  - NEA: Architects-in-Schools (Box 16, Folder 17)
  - NEA: City Edges - Cayuga Inlet Project, 1973 (Box 12, Folder 50)
  - NEA: City Options, 1974 (Box 12, Folder 51)
  - NEA: Conservation of Manmade Environment Proposal (Box 12, Folder 52)
  - National Register for Historic Places (Box 12, Folder 53)
  - National Trust for Historic Preservation (Box 12, Folder 54)
  - National Trust for Historic Preservation: Case Studies, 1976 (Box 12, Folder 55)
  - National Trust for Historic Preservation: Conserve Neighborhoods (Box 12, Folder 56)
  - National Trust for Historic Preservation: Historic Preservation, vol. 23, no.1, January-March 1971 (Box 12, Folder 57)
  - National Trust for Historic Preservation: Preservation News (Box 12, Folder 58)
  - National Trust for Historic Preservation: A Teacher's Guide to Preservation - Related Materials (Box 12, Folder 59)
  - New York State - New City Project, September-October 1969 (Box 12, Folder 60)
  - New York State Coastal Management Program (Box 12, Folder 61)
  - New York State Commission on the Restoration of the Capitol (Box 13, Folder 1)
  - New York State Commission on the Restoration of the Capitol (Box 13, Folder 2)
  - New York State Commission on the Restoration of the Capitol (Box 13, Folder 3)
  - New York State Commission on the Restoration of the Capitol: Draft of Scope of Work, July 1982 (Box 13, Folder 4)
  - New York State Commission on the Restoration of the Capitol: Design Review Committee, 1982 (Box 13, Folder 5)
  - New York State Commission on the Restoration of the Capitol: The Great Albany Time Machine Project (Box 13, Folder 6)
  - New York State Commission on the Restoration of the Capitol: Annual Report, January 31, 1987 (Box 13, Folder 7)
  - New York State Council on the Arts (Box 13, Folder 8)
  - New York State Council on the Arts: Proposal, 1977-1978 (Box 13, Folder 9)
  - New York State Council on the Arts: General File, 1979 (Box 13, Folder 10)
  - New York State Council on the Arts: Historic Preservation Planning Workshop, 1979 (Box 13, Folder 11)
  - New York State Council on the Arts: Journalistic Program (Box 13, Folder 12)
  - New York State Council on the Arts: AEA Panel - Correspondence other than notices, 1979-1980 (Box 13, Folder 13)
  - New York State Council on the Arts: AEA Panel - Notices of Meeting and Minutes, 1979-1980 (Box 13, Folder 14)
  - New York State Council on the Arts: AEA Panel - Proposals to be reviewed, 1979-1980 (Box 13, Folder 15)
  - New York State Council on the Arts: AEA Panel - Basic Background Information, 1980-1981 (Box 13, Folder 16)
  - New York State Council on the Arts: AEA Panel - Correspondence other than notices, 1980-1981 (Box 13, Folder 17)
  - New York State Council on the Arts: AEA Panel - Notices of Meetings and Minutes, 1980-1981 (Box 13, Folder 18)
  - New York State Council on the Arts: AEA Panel - Proposals to be reviewed, 1980-1981 (Box 13, Folder 19)
  - New York State Council on the Arts, 1984-1985 (Box 13, Folder 20)
  - New York State Department of Environmental Conservation (Box 13, Folder 21)
  - New York State Department of Environmental Conservation: Adirondacks (Box 13, Folder 22)
  - New York State Department of Environmental Conservation: Catskill Park, State Land Master Plan, May 1985 (Box 13, Folder 23)
  - New York State Department of Transportation: Barge Canal Planning & Development Board (Box 13, Folder 24)
  - New York State Department of Transportation: Barge Canal Planning & Development Board (Box 13, Folder 25)
  - New York State Department of Transportation: Barge Canal Planning & Development Board (Box 13, Folder 26)
  - New 1987-1988York State Department of Transportation: Barge Canal Planning & Development Board I. (Box 13, Folder 27)
  - New York State Department of Transportation: Barge Canal Planning & Development Board II., 1987-1988 (Box 13, Folder 28)
  - New York State Department of Transportation: ECO-TRANS (Citizens for Ecological Transportation Planning) - Rochester, N.Y. (Box 13, Folder 29)
  - New York State Department of Transportation: ECO-TRANS - Transportation Statement I. (Box 13, Folder 30)
  - New York State Department of Transportation: ECO-TRANS - Transportation Statement II. (Box 13, Folder 31)
  - New York State Division of Housing & Community Renewal: Proposal, 1979 (Box 13, Folder 32)
  - New York State Education Department (Box 13, Folder 33)
  - New York State Education Department: Blank Special Grant - Budget Amendment Summary Sheets, March 1969 (Box 13, Folder 34)
  - New York State Education Department: Center for Multinational and Comparative Education (Box 13, Folder 35)
  - New York State Education Department: Guidlines for Submission of Proposals (Box 13, Folder 36)
  - New York State Education Department: Prieto (Box 13, Folder 37)
  - New York State Education Department: Youth Employment Policy Task Force I. (Box 13, Folder 38)
  - New York State Education Department: Youth Employment Policy Task Force II. (Box 13, Folder 39)
  - New York State Main Street Alliance (Box 13, Folder 40)
  - New York State Main Street Alliance: Membership Directory, 1995 (Box 13, Folder 41)
  - New York State Main Street Center (Box 13, Folder 42)
  - New York State Planning (Box 13, Folder 43)
  - (49th) New York State Review Board: Meeting, February 26-27, 1987 (Box 13, Folder 44)
  - New York State Senate Special Committee on the Culture Industry: Recommendations, 1978 (Box 13, Folder 45)
  - New York State Senate Special Committee on the Culture Industry: Recommendations, 1983-1984 (Box 13, Folder 46)
  - New York - Temporary State Commission to Study the Catskills: Final Report, April 1975 (Box 13, Folder 47)
  - New York - Temporary State Commission on Tug Hill: Report, February 1976 (Box 13, Folder 48)
  - New York State Urban Cultural Parks Program (Box 13, Folder 49)
  - New York State Urban Cultural Parks Program, July 1987 (Box 13, Folder 50)
  - New York State Urban Cultural Parks Program: (I., II., III. from binder 1), 1986-1987 (Box 13, Folder 51)
  - New York State Urban Cultural Parks Program: (IV., V., VI., VII. from binder 1), 1986-1987 (Box 13, Folder 52)
  - New York State Urban Cultural Parks Program: (I., II., III. from binder 2), 1986-1987 (Box 13, Folder 53)
  - New York State Urban Cultural Parks Program: (IV., V., VI., VII. from binder 2), 1986-1987 (Box 13, Folder 54)
  - New York State Urban Cultural Parks Program: Rochester - Brown's Race, 1991 (Box 13, Folder 44)
  - Preservation League of New York (Box 14, Folder 1)
  - Preservation League of New York (Box 14, Folder 2)
  - Preservation League of New York (Box 14, Folder 3)
  - Preservation League of New York: Presentation (Box 14, Folder 4)
  - Preservation League of New York: Research Report on the Great Camps of the Adirondacks, June 1978 (Box 14, Folder 5)
  - Preservation League of New York: Coalition to Save Camp Sagamore in the Adirondacks (Box 14, Folder 6)
  - New York State: SEA Grant I. (Box 14, Folder 7)
  - New York State: SEA Grant II. (Box 14, Folder 8)
  - Regional Conference of Historical Agencies (RCHA): Landscape (Box 14, Folder 9)
  - United States Department of Health, Education & Welfare: Title I. - HEA - Environmental Awareness, 1975 (Box 14, Folder 10)
  - United States Department of Health, Education & Welfare: High Rock Park Conservation Center - Environmental Awareness, 1975 (Box 14, Folder 11)
- Miscellany
    - Miscellaneous (Box 14, Folder 12)
    - Miscellaneous (Box 14, Folder 13)
    - Miscellaneous (Box 14, Folder 14)
    - Architecture and Design Workshop - Sponsored by Tompkins, Seneca, and Tioga BOCES, March 22, 1983 (Box 14, Folder 15)
    - Boston Landmarks Commission (Box 14, Folder 16)
    - Central Winston-Salem Plan (Box 14, Folder 17)
    - Columbia University: Charles H. Revson Fellows Program, March 25, 1987 (Box 14, Folder 18)
    - Conley Group (Box 14, Folder 19)
    - Continuing Education Models: General Literature (Box 14, Folder 20)
    - Continuing Education: Bridging the Information Gap, December 1975 (Box 14, Folder 21)
    - Environmental Impact Statement, March 20, 1973 (Box 14, Folder 22)
    - Finger Lakes Association, Inc. (Box 14, Folder 23)
    - Massie Heritage Interpretation Center (Box 14, Folder 24)
    - National Growth Policy Study - Kermit C. Parsons, 1976 (Box 14, Folder 25)
    - New York City (Box 14, Folder 26)
    - New York City: Landmarks Preservation Commission (Box 14, Folder 27)
    - New York City: Office for Metropolitan History (Box 14, Folder 28)
    - New York Univeristy: New Careers Development Center - Bibliography of Materials Available (Box 14, Folder 29)
    - Nixon, Hargrave, Devans & Doyle (Box 14, Folder 30)
    - North Country Community College - Center for Humanities and Adirondack Studies (Box 14, Folder 31)
    - Pinelands Protection Act of 1979 - Pinelands, N.J. (Box 14, Folder 32)
    - Proposed Pyramid Mall - Williston, Vermont (Box 14, Folder 33)
    - Rochester Institute of Technology: Department of Extended Services - Leadership Development Workshop, 1969-1971 (Box 14, Folder 34)
    - Salem, N.H. (Box 14, Folder 35)
    - Seneca Falls, N.Y.: Poster - 1856 (Box 14, Folder 36)
    - Stockholm Conference, 1972 (Box 14, Folder 37)
    - Suggested Format for Radio Interview with Mayor Conley & Stuart Stein, [1975] (Box 14, Folder 38)
    - Stu's "Proverbial Archives" (Box 14, Folder 39)
    - Tioga County: District Profile (Box 14, Folder 40)
    - Torpedo Factory Art Center (Box 14, Folder 41)
    - Universidad de Puerto Rico: Graduate School of Planning (Box 14, Folder 42)
    - Univeristyof California, Berkeley: Continuing Education - Certificate Program in City Planning (Box 14, Folder 43)
    - Univeristy of Pennsylvania: CP 736 - Seminar on Urbanization in Developing Countries - Course Description, Spring 1969 (Box 14, Folder 44)
    - Univeristy of Pennsylvania: Transportation Readings and Course Material, 1973 (Box 14, Folder 45)
    - Univeristy of Pennsylvania: Transportation Readings and Course Material (Box 14, Folder 46)
    - Univeristy of Pennsylvania: Transportation Readings and Course Material - Articles (Box 14, Folder 47)
    - Univeristy of Washington: College of Architecture and Urban Planning (Box 14, Folder 48)
    - Workbook: First Draft Original I. (Box 14, Folder 49)
    - Workbook: First Draft Original II. (Box 14, Folder 50)
    - Zoning Ordinances (Box 14, Folder 51)
    - Westchester County, New York (Box 16, Folder 18)
  - Photographs & Negatives
    - Photographs, August 1993 (Box 15, Folder 1)
    - Photographs (Box 15, Folder 2)
    - Elmira: Base Map - Negative (Box 15, Folder 3)
    - Seneca Falls, New York (Box 16, Folder 19)
  - Articles, Newspapers & Clippings, Papers, Reports & Other Publications
    - Articles (Box 15, Folder 4)
    - Articles re: Soil Surveys (Box 15, Folder 5)
    - Articles re: Tompkins County (Box 15, Folder 6)
    - Newspapers & Clippings (Box 15, Folder 7)
    - Newspapers & Clippings (Box 15, Folder 8)
    - The Evening Sun - Chenengo County, N.Y., January 31, 1989 (Box 15, Folder 9)
    - The State Bank Chronicle - Seneca Falls, N.Y., October 22, 1980 (Box 15, Folder 10)
    - The Reveille, 125th Anniversary - Seneca Falls, N.Y., October 22, 1985 (Box 15, Folder 11)
    - The Reveille & Clippings - Seneca Falls, N.Y. (Box 15, Folder 12)
    - Watkins Review & Clippings - Watkins Glenn, N.Y. (Box 15, Folder 13)
    - Papers & Reports (Box 15, Folder 14)
    - Papers & Reports (Box 15, Folder 15)
    - Papers & Reports (Box 15, Folder 16)
    - Papers & Reports (Box 15, Folder 17)
    - Papers & Reports (Box 15, Folder 18)
    - Papers & Reports (Box 15, Folder 19)
    - Publications re: Architecture (Box 15, Folder 20)
    - Association of Collegiate Schools of Planning: The Bulletin (Box 15, Folder 21)
    - Government Publications (Legislative Reports, Bills, Laws, Acts, etc.) (Box 15, Folder 22)
    - Historic Preservation, April-June 1975 & March/April 1979 (Box 15, Folder 23)
    - Journal of Housing, Index 1969, August 1972 & February -March 1972 (Box 15, Folder 24)
    - Journal of Housing, February & March 1974 (Box 15, Folder 25)
    - Preservation Briefs (Box 15, Folder 26)
    - Publications re: Two-Year Colleges (Box 15, Folder 27)
    - World Bank (Box 15, Folder 28)
    - New York State Publications (Box 15, Folder 29)
    - Miscellaneous (Flyers, Brochures, Pamphlets, Newsletters, Bulletins, etc.) (Box 16, Folder 1)
    - Miscellaneous (Flyers, Brochures, Pamphlets, Newsletters, Bulletins, etc.) (Box 16, Folder 2)
    - Miscellaneous (Box 16, Folder 3)
    - Miscellaneous (Box 16, Folder 4)
    - Miscellaneous (Box 16, Folder 5)
    - Miscellaneous (Box 16, Folder 6)
    - Miscellaneous (Box 16, Folder 7)
    - Miscellaneous (Box 16, Folder 8)
    - Miscellaneous (Box 16, Folder 9)
    - Miscellaneous (Box 16, Folder 10)
    - Miscellaneous (Box 16, Folder 11)
    - Miscellaneous (Box 16, Folder 12)
    - A Community Renewal Program, Syracuse, New York (Box 16, Folder 20)